quizzes:
  - category: "Flags - Top 20 Economy Countries"
    questions:
      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "France"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: true, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "France flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "United States"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: true, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "USA flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "China"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: true, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "China flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Poland"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: true, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Poland flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Japan"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: true, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Japan flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Germany"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: true, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Germany flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "India"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: true, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "India flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Switzerland"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: true, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Switzerland flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "United Kingdom"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: true, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "UK flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Brazil"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: true, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Brazil flag"

